but better having seen all that of course that's the case in
their minds they're The Underdogs and that's how they justify
this I'm not responsible for every fucked up Rick out there
literally all say that they all have that excuse it's part of their
system none of them have to be responsible they're all victims of
themselves oh it's so hard to be a genius couldn't you
just die what are you doing about it jack shit I'm
leaving you know what the central finite curve is they built a wall
around Infinity we separated all the infinite universes
from all the infinite universes where he's the smartest man in the
universe every version of us has been every version of all of
our lives and one infinite crib built around an infinite
fucking baby b-but I'm leaving it that's what makes me
evil being sick of him if you've ever been sick of them
you've been evil to Rick you really leave the crows for
me or did you come back because they dumped you there you go
kid now you're evil Morty to sooner or later we
all are on this side of the Curve