the robin Step 1 admit to yourself that you still
have feelings for this girl I am hopelessly
irretrievably in love with her more than she knows
Step 2 choose the completely wrong moment to make a
drunken move after hanging out at a strip club the
robin Step 1 admit to yourself that you still have
feelings for this girl I am hopelessly
irretrievably in love with her more than she knows
Step 2 choose the completely wrong moment to make a
drunken move after hanging out at a strip club and get shot
down on purpose step 3 agree that you two don't
work locking the door on any future you could have together
I'm done trying to get you and get shot down on
purpose step 3 agree that you two don't work
locking the door on any future you could have together I'm
done trying to get you I can't do it anymore which will
drive Robin nuts step 4 robin goes
nuts step 5 find the person who annoys Robin
most in the world nobody asked for your help
I can't do it anymore which will drive Robin nuts
step 4 robin goes nuts step 5 find the person
who annoys Robin most in the world
nobody asked for your help Let's Race and
ask for her help hi Barney what are you doing here
actually I'm looking for you this may sound kind of weird
but I have a prop explain everything to Patrice and hope she
agrees to help what's right and ask for her
help hi Barney what are you doing here actually
I'm looking for you this may sound kind of weird but I have a
prop explain everything to Patrice and hope she agrees to
help of course I'll help step 6 check with your doctor
about possible broken ribs step 7 pretend to be
dating Patrice nobody ask you here actually I
did step 8 wait until Robin inevitably breaks into your
place to find the Playbook and show it to Patrice which you'll
monitor via the hidden cameras you have in your Apartments and
of course I'll help you step 6 check with your
doctor about possible broken ribs step 7 pretend to
be dating Patrice nobody asked you here
actually I did step 8 wait until Robin
inevitably breaks into your place to find the Playbook and show it to
Patrice which you'll monitor via the hidden cameras you have in your
Apartments Patrice the Robins in the nest that
means Robin broke into my apartment were you even
listening when I explain the codes step 9 after Patrice
finds the Playbook have your first big
fight it's going so well thank you so much
thank you next weekend know Patrice the
Robins in the nest that means Robin
broke into my apartment were you even listening when I explained the
codes step 9 after Patrice finds the
Playbook have your first big fight he's
going so well thank you so much next weekend
know prove your loyalty to Patrice by burning the
Playbook and actually burn it you don't need it
anymore Step 11 because your friends have no
boundaries they'll inevitably have an intervention for
Robin which you'll monitor via the hidden cameras you have in
Marshall and Lily's apartment step 12 tell only
Ted about your plan to propose to Patrice you can't tell
anybody prove your loyalty to Patrice by burning the
Playbook and actually burn it you don't need it
anymore Step 11 because your friends have no
boundaries they'll inevitably have an intervention for
Robin which you'll monitor via the hidden cameras you have in
Marshall and Lily's apartment step 12 tell only
Ted about your plan to propose to Patrice you can't
tell anybody agreed agreed Step
13 wait and see if Ted tells Robin and if he
does Barney's getting engaged it means your
best bro in the world has let go of Robin and has
given you his Blessing step 14 Robin arrives at her
favorite spot in the city and finds the secret
final page of the Playbook the last
play you'll ever run step 15
Robin realized Step 13 wait and see if Ted tells
Robin and if he does Barney's getting
engaged it means your best bro in the world
has let go of Robin and has given you his Blessing step
14 Robin arrives at her favorite spot in the city
and finds the secret final page of the
Playbook the last play you'll ever run
step 15 Robin realizes she's standing
underneath the mistletoe seriously Barney even
you even someone as certifiably
insane as you must realize that this is too far you
lied to me manipulated me for weeks today do you
really think I could ever kiss you after that izes she standing
underneath the mistletoe seriously Barney even
you even someone as certifiably
insane as you must realize that this is too far you
lied to me manipulated me for weeks today do you
really think I could ever kiss you after that do you really think I could ever
trust you after that this this is
proof of why we don't work why we'll never work do you really
think I could ever trust you after that this
this is proof of why we don't work why we'll never
work so thank you you set me free because
how could I be with a man who thinks that this
trick this enormous like could ever
make me want to date him again so thank you you set me
free because how could I be with a man who thinks that
this trick does enormous like
could ever make me want to date him again turn it over turn it
over Robin Scherbatsky Robin
Scherbatsky will you marry me will you marry me
India in the